[
    {
       "question": "In Python args is presented with tuple",
       "options": ["yes", "no"],
       "correct_answer": "yes"
     },
     {
      "question": "In Python kwargs is presented with dictionary",
      "options": ["yes", "no"],
      "correct_answer": "yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "kw in kwargs is",
      "options": ["keyword", "knowledge"],
      "correct_answer": "keyword"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Python, a ... is an argument that is passed to a function by position or order",
      "options": ["positional argument", "keyword argument"],
      "correct_answer": "positional argument"
    },
    {
      "question": "greet(name='Bob', age=30) is an example of ...",
      "options": ["kwargs", "args"],
      "correct_answer": "kwargs"
    },
    {
      "question": "For kwargs position is ...",
      "options": ["not important", "important"],
      "correct_answer": "not important"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Python, 'def add(x: int, y: int) -> int:' this function is example of ...",
      "options": ["annotation type", "container type", "abstract type"],
      "correct_answer": "annotation type"
    },
    {
      "question": "Annotations in Python are primarily used for ...",
      "options": ["faster code compilation", "code readability and documentation"],
      "correct_answer": "code readability and documentation"
    },
    {
      "question": "in Python, lambda function is a no name function",
      "options": ["yes", "no", "it is not a function at all"],
      "correct_answer": "yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "The ... provides a concise way to write an if-else statement in a single line.",
      "options": ["walrus operator", "ternary operator"],
      "correct_answer": "ternary operator"
    },
    {
      "question": "'maximum = a if a > b else b' is an example of ternary operator",
      "options": ["yes", "no"],
      "correct_answer": "yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Python, there are ... copy",
      "options": ["shallow/copy and deep", "metadata"],
      "correct_answer": "shallow/copy and deep"
    },
    {
      "question": "Deep copy ... ",
      "options": ["keeps references to object only", "recursively creates copies of all nested objects within the original object"],
      "correct_answer": "recursively creates copies of all nested objects within the original object"
    },
    {
      "question": "Poetry is ...",
      "options": ["installer, project dependencies manager, handles packaging, and provides tools for building and publishing packages", "a package installer", "another name of pip"],
      "correct_answer": "installer, project dependencies manager, handles packaging, and provides tools for building and publishing packages"
    },
    {
      "question": "pip downloads all packages from ...",
      "options": ["internet via search engine", "pypi.org"],
      "correct_answer": "pypi.org"
    },
    {
      "question": "in Python, a set is implemented as ...",
      "options": ["an array", "a hash table"],
      "correct_answer": "a hash table"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Python, lists are implemented as ...",
      "options": ["a traditional array", "a dynamic array with automatic resizing, like in C"],
      "correct_answer": "a dynamic array with automatic resizing, like in C"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Python, sets do not support indexing",
      "options": ["support", "does not support"],
      "correct_answer": "does not support"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Python, a hash table is implemented as a ...",
      "options": ["dictionary", "ndarray", "list"],
      "correct_answer": "dictionary"
    },
    {
      "question": "hash table uses ... function for index mapping",
      "options": ["md5", "hash function"],
      "correct_answer": "hash function"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Python, Collision Handling belongs to hash indexing topic",
      "options": ["yes, multiple keys might produce the same hash code", "no, it is related to concurrency topic"],
      "correct_answer": "yes, multiple keys might produce the same hash code"
    },
    {
      "question": "Class attributes are variables that are shared by all instances of a class",
      "options": ["yes", "no"],
      "correct_answer": "yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "Instance attributes are specific to each instance",
      "options": ["yes", "no"],
      "correct_answer": "yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "Decorators are implemented via classes",
      "options": ["yes", "no"],
      "correct_answer": "yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "'syntactic' sugar aims ",
      "options": ["to replace cane sugar with sweeteners", "to make the code more readable or expressive"],
      "correct_answer": "to make the code more readable or expressive"
    },
    {
      "question": "dic = {1: 2, 3: 4, 3: 5, 4: 5, 5: 6}<br>print(tuple(dic)) returns",
      "options": ["(1, 3, 4, 5)", "(2, 4, 5, 6)", "run-time error, it is illegal transformation"],
      "correct_answer": "(1, 3, 4, 5)"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Python, class is an object as well",
      "options": ["yes", "no"],
      "correct_answer": "yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "Metaclasses are powerful but should be used judiciously, as they introduce ...",
      "options": ["restrictions to architecture", "complexity"],
      "correct_answer": "complexity"
    },
    {
      "question": "",
      "options": ["", "", ""],
      "correct_answer": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "",
      "options": ["", "", ""],
      "correct_answer": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "",
      "options": ["", "", ""],
      "correct_answer": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "",
      "options": ["", "", ""],
      "correct_answer": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "",
      "options": ["", "", ""],
      "correct_answer": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "",
      "options": ["", "", ""],
      "correct_answer": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "",
      "options": ["", "", ""],
      "correct_answer": ""
    }

    
     
   ]
   